mymls.com 2018-11-11

# Privacy Policy

This website is brought to you by:

REcolorado  
6455 South Yosemite Street, Suite 500  
Greenwood Village, CO 80111  
303.850.9576

At REcolorado, we are fully committed to the protection and security of any information you provide to us as visitors to our website. We want you to know that we truly respect and will protect your privacy, so you can enjoy using our site in your search for properties in the Denver Colorado area. This is the Privacy Policy for the REcolorado.com website. This Privacy Policy discloses our approach to privacy and how your personal information is collected and used. Your use of our website constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your consent to the practices it describes. 

### What Information We Collect

Generally speaking, our website is informational. Your “personally identifiable information,” that is, information about you as an individual which would permit someone to contact you, such as your email address, is only provided if you email us with questions or for any other reason. Otherwise, we do not collect any personally identifiable information from you unless you voluntarily provide it.

As is the case when you visit most websites, to administer our site, your visit triggers the automatic logging of certain anonymous information about your computer system such as the type of browser you use, the server name and your “IP” (Internet Protocol) address. When your web browser or email application requests a web page or email from another computer using the Internet, it automatically gives that computer your computer’s “address” so it knows where it should send the information. This is called your computer’s “IP address.” This anonymous information does not contain any personally identifiable information.

### How We Protect Your Information

We also want you to know that we take the security of your information very seriously and that we take appropriate measures to protect the files in our data system. You need to know, however, that due to the open communication nature of the Internet we cannot guarantee that communication between you and us, and between us and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties nor can we be responsible for information stolen from our servers by information harvesting software which may have the ability to scrape data.

### Third Party Sites and Applications

REcolorado.com uses third party applications. These third party applications may collect information about your interaction with these applications. Your use of these third party applications is subject to their respective Terms and other policies, if applicable. REcolorado.com includes links to other third party websites. These third party websites may collect information about you. Your use of these third party websites is subject to their respective Terms and other policies, if applicable. We are not responsible for the availability of any other site to which this site links. We do not take responsibility for the contents, advertising, products, privacy policies or other material made available through any other site. Please direct your concerns to that other site’s webmaster or appropriate contact. 

### We Do Not Sell or Rent Your Personally Identifiable Information

If you provide personally identifiable information to us, please know we do not share your personally identifiable information with third parties for promotional use without your consent. We may, however, have to disclose, transfer, sell or assign any information obtained through this website, or otherwise in our possession, to a third party as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of REcolorado. We may also have to make information obtained through this website, or otherwise in our possession, available to law enforcement personnel and agencies when requested to do so or as required by law.

### Cookie Technology

Cookie technology is employed when you access our site. The purpose of cookies is for us to track the uses of our site. “Cookies” are small text files sent by Web servers to be stored on the computers of website users. These files often contain personalization settings or unique identifiers, to keep track of your information and to help us understand the movements of users within and between websites. Cookies alone do not personally identify individuals. One may, however disallow receiving cookies at any time through the web browser settings.

### Opting Out of Behavioral Advertising

REcolorado adheres to the guidelines of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising, and has implemented opt-out procedures in accordance with those organizations’ programs. Some of our advertising service providers may also be members and offer an opt-out of behavioral advertising. You may want to visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), which provides information regarding targeted advertising and the opt-out offered by NAI members. You may also want to visit [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), which provides an opt-out by participating companies in the DAA Self-Regulatory Program. If you would like to opt-out of behavioral advertising controlled by REcolorado you may visit the NAI and DAA links provided above. Please note that REcolorado and other companies may still collect information when you are online and opting out through these mechanisms does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to be served generic ads while online.

### Privacy Statement Changes

We reserve the right to change or amend our Privacy Policy to address new issues of privacy and information security and to reflect changes to our website or business practices. Any new changes and/or amendments will be posted on this page. Each version of this policy may be identified by its effective date which is located at the top of the page.

### Questions About Our Privacy And Information Security Practices?

Your visit to this site is subject to both this notice and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes and application of the law of the State of Colorado. If you have any questions about our privacy practices or procedures, please feel free to email us at [privacy@REcolorado.com](mailto:privacy@REcolorado.com). We will promptly address your inquiry.
